天使们 盛宴即将开始
各位请准备
开场了
女士们 先生们
欢迎来到维多利亚的秘密之夜
四十位天使都请就位
各位抓紧
后台人员到位
舞台布景就绪
蕾哈娜从化妆间出来了
布鲁诺·马尔斯已到后台
好的 谢谢
贾斯汀·比伯到了
还有两分钟就开场
天使们 候场了
马上开场 马上开场 谢谢
静一静 马上开场
阿德里亚娜准备
坎蒂丝 二号机
琳赛正上台 琳赛上台
杜鲁筝 候场中
艾琳到了 艾琳已就位
亚历山大已就位
独一无二的米兰达
下面是莉莉
贝哈蒂请尽快
全部模特上台 全部上台
走吧 她上台了
好的 很好 来吧 加油
女士们 先生们
欢迎来到独一无二的
维多利亚的秘密时尚内衣秀现场
The Doors - “Break on Through”
You know the day destroys the night
Night divides the day
Tried to run, tried to hide
Break on through to the other side
Break on through to the other side, yeah
We chased our pleasures here
Dug our treasures there
But can you still recall the time we cried
Break on through to the other side
Break on through to the other side, yeah
Go, get your freak on, go, get your freak on
Go, get your freak on
Go, get your, get your freak on
Missy be puttin' it down
I'm the hottest round
I told y'all mother, y'all can't stop me now
Listen to me now
I'm lasting 20 rounds
And if you want me, people, come on get me now
Is you with me now
Then biggie biggie bounce
I Know you dig the way I switch my style
Go, get your freak on, go, get your freak on
Go, get your freak on
Go, get your, get your freak on
Last night a little dancer
Came dancin' to my door
Last night a little angel
Came pumpin' cross my floor
She said, come on, baby
I got a license for love
And if it expires
Pray help from above
Because in the midnight hour
She cried more, more, more
With a rebel yell
In the midnight hour, babe
More, more, more
With a rebel yell, more, more, more
Oh, yeah little angel
She want more
More, more, more, more, more
《奇幻马戏》
最后一位天使已下台
完毕
请后退一些
请后退一些 天使们要下台了
大换装哟
什么是性感?
作为维多利亚的秘密天使最大的好处
就是能参与拍摄维多利亚的秘密的广告
维多利亚的秘密广告都很经典华丽
描绘出自信强势的女性形象
真我本色 接不接受随你
跟其他电视广告完全不同
我看到的第一个维多利亚的秘密广告
是克劳迪娅·希弗拍的 被禁播的那段
销魂广告
感官享受
那个已经很保守了
风靡
全网
那时的内衣比我们现在穿的保守多了
时代确实改变了
我看没什么不对的
And it feels like I am
Just too close to love you
渴望是什么
很复杂
谁忘得了阿德瑞娜那个超级碗广告
活力十足性感有趣
她坐在那里
玩着手中的橄榄球
用她那迷人的眼睛望着你
阿德瑞娜·利玛的眼神就像在说
“看我多性感”
大家都注意到那广告
对球赛倒没那么有兴趣了
那就是阿德瑞娜的魔力
我们拍摄了整整五天
只为那30秒的广告
我们去了很多华丽的外景地
法国城堡那支广告
是我的最爱之一 超级浪漫
我认为那支广告
是维多利亚的秘密广告中最美的一段
那支假日广告是在芝加哥拍摄的
芝加哥是我的故乡
整个拍摄过程都赞极了
布拉格之旅超棒
城市也很漂亮
很梦幻
我们走进这座绝美的城堡
古色古香大理石拱门
地板上还铺满玫瑰花瓣
如梦如幻
而且超级性感
鲍勃·迪伦 美国著名歌手
在威尼斯与鲍勃·迪伦的拍摄
能和他一起拍摄真是难以置信
I'm sick of it all
他可是天王级人物
他从来不拍广告
我与迈克尔·贝的第一次合作
实在棒极了
与他合作拍广告
就像在拍詹姆斯·邦德的电影
劲爆夸张
让我肾上腺素飙升
维多利亚的秘密广告的规模 质量和疯狂程度
都在逐年激增
今年也是一样
我最激动的是蕾哈娜要来
蕾哈娜超赞
她的表演一定很棒
蕾哈娜 我超爱她 超棒的
我从来没见过她真人演唱会什么的
所以我迫不及待啦
她台风超劲 完全掌控舞台
伙计们 我这边准备好了 待命了
舞台准备好了 只等女神出场
她一来咱们就可以开始了
请让蕾哈娜准备
我一定会很嗨的
贝哈蒂候场
“危险通话”音乐视频就位
三  二  一
女士们 先生们 掌声欢迎蕾哈娜
《危险通话》
Rihanna - “Diamonds”
Shine bright like a diamond
Find light in the beautiful sea
I choose to be happy
You and I, you and I
We're like diamonds in the sky
You're a shooting star I see
A vision of ecstasy
When you hold me, I'm alive
We're like diamonds in the sky
I knew that we'd become one
Right away
Oh, right away
At first sight
I felt the energy of sun rays
I saw the life inside your eyes
Tonight you and I
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Eye to eye
So alive
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Shine bright like a diamond
Shining bright like a diamond
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Shine bright like a diamond
Shining bright like a diamond
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Palms rise to the universe
As we moonshine and molly
Feel the warmth, we'll never die
We're like diamonds in the sky
You're a shooting star I see
A vision of ecstasy
When you hold me, I'm alive
We're like diamonds in the sky
I knew that we'd become one
Right away
I saw the life inside your eyes
Tonight
You and I
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Eye to eye
So alive
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Shine bright like a diamond
Shining bright like a diamond
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Shine bright like a diamond
Shining bright like a diamond
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Shine bright like a diamond
So shine bright
Tonight
You and I
We're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
Eye to eye, so alive
Shine bright like a diamond
Whoa-yay
Shine bright Like a diamond
Shine bright like a diamond
去年维多利亚的秘密秀落幕的闪粉一落地
我们就开始筹备今年的秀了
准备工作持续了一整年
我们希望维多利亚的秘密秀一年比一年高端
这得要大量的时间和规划才能完成
我们的灵感来自各处
被电影或音乐触动
很多时候则是从维多利亚秘密的内衣系列里
得到新的启发
这次有个单元 名为“月历女郎”
“月历女郎”的主题
是50年代的复古女性
像蒂塔·万提斯的风格
开场时用可爱的新年装代表一月
结束时则用性感的圣诞女神来代表十二月
性感迷人的精髓贯穿全年的每个月
五月是设计定型的时候
我们的草图变成了实物
每一件内衣都是纯手工的高端定制品
我们与全世界最强悍的手艺人合作
制布人
图样创作者
珠宝设计师
一件内衣可能得经过五双手的打造
九月是开学的日子
要开始试衣了
还要打磨细节
一年前我们就开始考虑
姑娘们适合哪种服装哪种主题
我很开心因为今年我会穿上
价值二百五十万的花样胸衣
直到试装当日
一切才见分晓
之前都不知道穿上会是什么样
实在完美
这是我今年试穿的第一件
这是“月历女郎”的开场服装
非常漂亮 很兴奋 我喜欢这顶帽子
姑娘们都很棒
她们懂得如何展示服装
让服装充满了生命力
天桥秀上见
艾琳请就位 让艾琳过来
斯蒂夫 我们还在打理艾琳的造型
帽子要掉下来了
不行 得把帽子戴回去
快帮忙啊
拜托了 她得准时上场啊 知道了
女生们 先生们 掌声有请布鲁诺·马尔斯
《月历女郎》
Oh, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
无所谓
随便来一个吧  好
倒数  三  二  一
走吧
Never had much faith
走啊 艾琳
她走上天桥了
Never want to put my heart on deny
But swimming in your world is something spiritual
Spiritual
I'm born again every time
You spend the night
Because your sex takes me to paradise
Yeah, your sex takes me to paradise
And it shows
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Because you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
Yeah, you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
For too long, oh, oh
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah
You bring me to my knees
You make me testify
Testify
Yeah, you make a sinner change his ways
But open up your gates because I can't wait to see the light
To see the light
And right there is where I wanna stay
Because your sex takes me to paradise
Yeah, your sex takes me to paradise
And it shows
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Because you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
Yeah, you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Can I just stay here
Spend the rest of my days here
Because you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
Yeah, you make me feel like
I've been locked out of heaven
For too long
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah
谢谢
女生们 先生们 掌声有请贾斯汀·比伯
Justin Bieber - “As Long As You Love Me”
As long as you love me, girl
Ooh, yeah
We're under pressure
Seven billion people in the world trying to fit in
Keep it together
Smile on your face
Even though your heart is frowning
But hey now, you know, girl
We both know it's a cruel world
But I will take my chances
As long as you love me
We could be starving
We could be homeless
We could be broke
As long as you love me
I'll be your platinum
I'll be your silver, and I'll be your gold
As long as you love, love, love, love, love
Love, love, love, love, love me
Love, love, love, love, love me, love me
I don't know if this makes sense, but
You're my hallelujah, uh-huh
Give me a time or place, and I'll rendezvous
I'll fly you to it, I'll beat you there
Girl, you know I got you
Us, trust a couple things I can't spell without you
We're on top of the world 'cause that's just how we do
Used to tell me sky's the limit
Now the sky's our point of view
Now we're stepping out, like wow (Oh God)
Camera's pointed shoot
Ask me what's my best side
I stand back and point at you, you, you
The one that I argue with
Feel like I need a new girl to be bothered with
But the grass ain't always greener on the other side
It's green where you water it
So I know we got issues, baby
True, true, true
But I'd rather work on this with you
Than to go ahead and start with someone
As long as you love me we could be starving
We could be homeless
We could be broke
As long as you love me
I'll be your platinum, I'll be your silver
And I'll be your gold
As long as you la, la-la, la, la, la, la-la, la
La, la-la, la-la, la-la, love me
As long as you la, la-la, la
La, la, la-la, la
La, la-la, la-la, la-la, love me
As long you love me, yeah
Whoa, whoa
Ooh, baby
As long as you love me, yeah
来吧
谢谢
“粉红舞会”单元音乐跟拍就绪
Karmin - “Broken Hearted”
Uh-oh, that's right
On this video do anything you want to
So can finish what we started?
Don't you leave me broken-hearted tonight
Come on
That's right
Cheerio, uh.
《粉红舞会》
“粉红舞会”准备开始
这边五位美女已就位
Justin Bieber - “Beauty and a Beat”
Show you off, uh, uh
Tonight I wanna show you off
Hey, hey, hey
What you got
Uh, uh, a billion could've never bought
Uh, hey, hey, hey
We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight
I wanna show you all the finer things in life
So just forget about the world
We young tonight
I'm comin' for ya, I'm comin' for ya
'Cause all I need
Is beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
It's all 'bout you
When the music makes yo move
Baby, do it like you do
走起
Body rock
I want to feel your body rock
Hey, hey, hey
What you got
Uh, a billion could've never bought
Hey, hey, hey
We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight
I wanna show you all the finer things in life
So just forget about the world
We young tonight
I'm comin' for ya, I'm comin' for ya
'Cause all I need
Is a beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
一起来吧
It's all 'bout you
When the music makes you move
Baby, do it like you do
In time, ink lines
Bitches couldn't get on my incline
World tours, it's mine
Ten little letters and a big sign
Justin Bieber
You know I'm-a hit 'em with the ether
Buns out, wiener
But I gotta keep a eye out for Selena(r)
Beauty, Beauty and the Beast, Beauty from the east
Beautiful confessions to the priest
Beast, beauty from the streets
We don't get to cease every time
Beauty on the beats, beats
Body rock
Oh, I wanna feel your body rock
一起来吧
'Cause all I need
Is a beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
Yeah, yeah
It's all 'bout you
When the music makes you move
Baby, do it like you do
一起来
谢谢
约会是最好的发明了
我们都喜欢约会
约会很简单的
感觉对了你就知道了
他可能是那个真命天子呢
我喜欢自信而低调的男生
不需要故意显摆自己
我喜欢大手
还有宽厚的肩膀
超帅的喔
感觉他随时都能抱起你来
随时公主抱
It's always a good time...
我喜欢鲜花
哪怕奥兰多天天送花
行啊 我也觉得不够
就想找个身材超棒的帅哥 开玩笑啦
下一个问题 快跳过
'Cause it's always a good time...
我最糗的一次约会是看电影时睡着了
我趴在桌上
想跟他说悄悄话
天哪 结果蜡烛把我头发点着了
不是吧 他拿起纸巾
狂拍我头发
It's gonna be all right...
第一次接吻的感觉
怎样 就像...
Whoa, oh-oh, oh, oh, oh, oh...
我第一次接吻可不怎么样
就纳闷 该怎么做啊
我脑袋该往哪偏
我从不会第一次约会就接吻
我有过
喜欢他就表达出来呗
It's always a good time, good time...
我的初吻要留到婚礼
我对男生们的第一点建议是
做自己就好 淡定而自信
这样就够棒了
要风趣 有幽默感啦
没幽默细胞就别肉麻当有趣了
那真是 你可以努力啦
要表现出尊重 要有礼貌
那样会很性感 对
布鲁诺和乐队预备
音乐天才驾到
上场了 快快快
谢谢 抱歉 借过啦
布鲁诺和乐队现场表演即将开始
《银幕天使》
Bruno Mars - “Young Girls”
I spent all my money
Bought a big ol' fancy car
For these bright-eyed honeys
Oh, yeah, you know who you are
Keep me up till the sun is high
Till the birds start calling my name
I'm addicted and I don't know why
Guess I've always been this way
All these roads steer me wrong
But I still drive them all night long
All night long
All you young, wild girls
You make a mess of me
Yeah, you young, wild girls
You'll be the death of me
The death of me
All you young, wild girls
No matter what you do
Yeah, you young, wild girls
I'll always come back to you
Come back to you
I get lost under these lights
I get lost in the words I say
Start believing my own lies
Like everything will be okay
Oh, I still dream of a simple life
Boy meets girl, makes her his wife
But love don't exist when you live like this
That much I know
Yes, I know
All these roads steer me wrong
But I still drive them all night long
All night long
All you young, wild girls
You make a mess of me
Yeah, you young, wild girls
You'll be the death of me
The death of me
All you young, wild girls
No matter what you do
Yeah, you young, wild girls
I'll always come back to you
Come back to you
Ooh, you
You
Sure, you
Yeah, you
You
All you young, wild girls
You make a mess of me
Yeah, you young, wild girls
You'll be the death of me
The death of me
All you young, wild girls
No matter what you do
Yeah, you young, wild girls
I'll always come back to you
Come back to you
你好 性感大秀
坎蒂丝如同巨星运动员一样难得
她真是万里挑一的美人
I want Candy
她已成为超级巨星
这十年最具魅力的模特 非她莫属
我在南非的一个大农场里长大
你叫什么呀
坎蒂丝
我总是沉浸在自己的小天地里
我曾经特别害羞
但是我很喜欢旅行
对南非以外的世界着迷
一直很喜欢追求时尚和美容装扮
我要去跳芭蕾舞啦
我十五岁时被星探发现
当时我正和妈妈逛跳蚤市场
两年后
我便搬至纽约
第一次来到纽约
我充满了敬畏 纽约就像个外星球
坎蒂丝第一次来是做试衣模特
也就是说她过来替人试穿服装
让我们想象在秀场模特正式穿上
会是怎么样的效果
Mama told me not to waste my life...
准备好了吗 好了
她一走进来就好像是
“这是哪个天仙下凡啊”
太可爱了
Spread your wings
My little butterfly
不可思议
我从没见过哪个模特
穿什么都一样惊艳完美无缺
所以我们也让她加入走秀
They're made to fly
她一出场我们就认定
她一定会成为世界名模
我第一次被人们真正关注
就是我在维多利亚的秘密秀上出现之后
坎蒂丝当时真是红透了半边天
她为意大利版《Vogue》杂志拍摄封面
大幅彩照登上各类杂志
These wings are made to fly
我真的非常非常幸运
能与一些圈内人士合作
知名摄影师
比如马里奥·特斯蒂诺
分别为Chanel设计总监及著名摄影师
卡尔·拉格斐和泰利·理查森
我就这样成了超模 真是不可思议
我都不知道自己是怎么红的
但是我想如果没有维多利亚的秘密
我恐怕什么都不是吧
我要和蕾哈娜一同登场
好了
坎蒂丝呢
坎蒂丝还没来
她来了
女士们 先生们
有请蕾哈娜二度登台
《花为霓裳》
Rihanna - “Phresh Out The Runway”
I see you walk
Da-bi-da-bi-da-bi-do
In-any-uh-la
Love it, then come and get it
I know that you're with it
You see me, you like it, huh
Heel Givenchy, huh
Love it, then play it back
Plus where the 40 at
I'm, your cheap thrill
On top of my 50 mill
He eating the cake, killer
Own it, but don't kill her
My jewels are diamond rollers
My rock, chinchilla
Some more raw fun
I'm rolling like rock stars
Got 50, in my watch
With my Bentz down
Phresh out the runway, phresh out
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
I see you walk
Da-bi-da-bi-da-bi-do
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
I see you walk
Phresh out the runway, phresh out, phresh out
Hold up
Venus, I'm out of coast
My (bitches) don't know
(F*ck) with 'em my designer drip to the (f*cking) floor
Be out in that
They like 'em in all them honey stuff
Rollin' so bowliners
And my (bitches) saw Bugatti
Bodies of Ducatis
They'll do what the (f*ck) you want
My (niggas gon' be like bitch this my f*cking song)
How could you be so hood, but you so (f*cking) pop
How could you be so fun
And sound like you selling rocks
What's in the chain dollars
All of the bank dollars got change
For small dollars
Everything plain dollars
I'm standing in the bank line
You throwing up your gang sign
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
Phresh, phresh out the runway
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
I see you walk
Da-bi-da-bi-da-bi-do
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out
Hold up
I bet you want to know what my crew about
You really want to know
How we get down
Walked up in this (bitch) like we own this ho
Own this ho
Like we own this ho
I bet you want to know what I'm all about
You really want to know
How I get down
Walked up in this (bitch) like we own this ho
Own the ho
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
Ph-Phresh out the the runway phresh out
Phresh out the runway, phresh
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
Phresh
Phresh out the runway
I see you walk
Da-bi-da-bi-da-bi-do
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
I hear you walk
Phresh out the runway, phresh out, phresh out
Hold up
Phresh out, phresh out the runway
Phresh out the runway
Phresh out, phresh out
Ph-Phresh out, ph-phresh out the runway
蕾哈娜即将下台
谢幕候场 全体模特上台
谢幕啦 谢幕啦
太棒了
上台 让全体模特上台
全体模特上台
正在上场
Rudimental - “Feel The Love”
模特们正在上场
You know I said it's true
I can feel the power, can you feel it, too
I can feel it all
You know I said it's true
I can feel the power, can you feel it, too
I can feel it all
I can feel it all, I can feel it all
You know I said it's true
I can feel the power, can you feel it, too
I can feel it all, I can feel it all
You know I said it's true
I can feel the power, can you feel it, too
I can feel it, I can feel it
又一届维多利亚的秘密落幕了
明年见
比伯太赞了
我的天 还有布鲁诺 爱你哟
维多利亚的秘密花絮
不好意思我们在采访呢
你所有的梦想...
马上到场
绿色的
我脚上有东西
你们一定要把这段剪掉
给点时间我考虑一下
我再说一次
怎么说来着
身体 身体 身体 身体 身体
那是什么
这说的哪国语言
我有个想法
就这么说吧
收工啦
去派对狂欢啦